bada-parda.com 2008-09-05

# ChotaParda.com: Privacy

www.chotaparda.com - has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for [ www.chotaparda.com](http://www.chotaparda.com/)

Cookies:

Our Site, like most other sites, uses cookies to provide you with a more personalized and user-friendly experience. A cookie is a message that is sent to a browser from a Web server and stored on your computerï¿½s hard drive. Cookies help us keep track of the size of our audience, the frequency of visits to our Site and the areas that are most popular. If a guest makes a purchase, cookies are used to keep the shopping cart active during the shopping process. We may also use cookies to help us deliver content or advertising specific to your interests, and to save your preferences or passwords so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit our Site. Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, but then your preferences, passwords and other information will not be saved, and you may have to re-enter information to use certain features of our Site. 

We may also log IP addresses for the purposes of systems administration or to report information in aggregate form to our advertisers (e.g., how many visitors logged in to our Web site). In some cases your IP address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer Internet access provider such as AOL or Earthlink or Satyam, chances are that your IP address varies each sessionï¿½thus making it effectively impossible for us to use your IP address (by itself) to determine who you are. 

Advertisement:

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies delivered through banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. www.chotaparda.com may also serve banner ads that contain cookies. We will only share such information with our advertisers and sponsors on an aggregate basis to determine the success of any given banner, logo or advertisement.

The Site contains links and advertisements to other sites. If you click-through a banner ad or link and submit your information to that advertiser or site, you will be subject to their own privacy practices. www.chotaparda.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

Public Forums Rules and Policies:

The Site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and that if you disclose personal contact information in these areas, others may use it to send you unsolicited messages so you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.. We do not control the actions of our guests and registered members. www.chotaparda.com encourages our users to be smart about choosing when, and to whom to release information online.

Of course there are many other ways we conceivably could get information from or about you that are not described elsewhere in this Statement. For example, you might email us through one of our customer service email addresses, or we may get a complaint about you from a third party. Our practices with respect to such information are pretty much as youï¿½d expect -- we use and disclose this information in a commercially reasonable business manner. 

You agree not to use forum to post any material which is vulgar, defamatory, inaccurate, harassing, hateful, threatening, invading of others privacy, sexually oriented, or violates any laws. You also agree that you will not post any copyrighted material that is not owned by yourself or the owners of these forums. 

You remain solely responsible for the content of your messages, and you agree to indemnify and hold harmless this forum and their agents with respect to any claim based upon any post you may make. We also reserve the right to reveal whatever information we know about you in the event of a complaint or legal action arising from any message posted by yourself.

Although messages posted are not the responsibility of this forum and we are not responsible for the content or accuracy of any of these messages, we reserve the right to delete any message for any or no reason whatsoever. If you do find any posts are objectionable then please contact Us. We delete the objectionable from our forums. 

The Federal Trade Commission's Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) requires that Web Sites are to obtain parental consent before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from children under 13. If you are a minor under 13, you are prohibited from submitting anything in forums.

Security:

This site has industry consistent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. But since the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure, www.chotaparda.com assumes no liability for disclosure of data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized third parties. 

## Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [ contact Us](http://www.chotaparda.com/contact%20us.asp)

By using the Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Statement. If you are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Statement, you may feel free to e-mail us with questions or concerns, but your only remedy is to discontinue use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time.
